S. M. Sarowar

Web Developer

Im a Software Engineering graduate and experienced in web development. Though I'm working on PHP with Laravel framework. I'm open to switching any platform as per need. My quick adaptability helps me to keep pace with the organization's goals.



smsarowar4@gmail.com

+8801677997957

Dhaka, Bangladesh

linkedin.com/in/s-m-sarowar-998892219? in utm_source=share&utm_campaign=shar e_via&utm_content=profile&utm_mediu m=android_app&fbclid=IwAR06E9C6

github.com/mdsarowar 💭

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Debeloper

BiddaBari

12/2023 - Present

Dhaka, Bangladesh

- BoiBari website development.
- BoiBari is a Book related ecommerce website like rokomari.
- Bkash payment gateway integrate in this website.

Jr. Developer SYS Dev Ltd

08/2022 - 08/2023

Dhaka

- web development & documentation
- Contribute Dynamic form create & submit
- Requirement collect
- software training

Web Developer

Cosmic IT

03/2022 - 08/2022

Dhaka, Bangladesh

(remote)

- News Portal link: https://bdnewsbook24.net/home
- Contribute school management
- Library management

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

Daffodil International University

01/2018 - 03/2022 Dhaka, Dhanmondi

software engineer CGPA: 3.66

HSC

Dr.Khandaker Mosharraf Hossain College

01/2015 - 03/2017

Comilla, Daudkandi

Science GPA: 4.00

SKILLS

PHP C Programming Problem Solving

ACHIEVEMENTS

DIU SWE Intra Department Programming contest.

First time-20th & Second time 9th

PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-commerce

Through this system everyone can buy product with cash on delevery

CERTIFICATES

PHP with Laravel (01/2022 - 04/2022)

BASIS Institute of Technology & Management (BITM)

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

BASIS Institute of Technology & Management (BITM) (01/2022 - 04/2022)

web development

SYS Dev Ltd (08/2022 - 08/2023)

Web Development

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Web Development

Embedded Programming